Teammate Code Contributions:

Kobe Oley:
Developed the sql_helper.py file
Did the bulk of the data engineering portion (data migration, data integrity, normalization)
Created the System Architecture and Database UML diagrams
Researched and incorporated work into all sections of the report, except Data analysis.
Wrote specifically about the legality of the data collection, all of the data engineering section, and the most of the Motivationa and goals section

Kolbe Yang:
Did data analysis and wrote report sections associated with
- genres.py
- by_year.py
Researched and wrote the Related Work section of the project
Researched and wrote the Legal and Ethical Considerations of the project report
Completed the Conclusion section of the report